A Guide to the Sellers Family Papers, 1847-1965
Library of Virginia
Library of Virginia
Sellers Family Papers, 1847-1965
The Library of Virginia
51955
16.55 cubic feet (39 boxes)
Sellers Family
Administrative Information
Access Restrictions
There are no restrictions.
Acquisition Information
Donated by Louis Michael Tate.
Biographical Information
The Sellers family was a prominent Texan family, with strong ties to Virginia. Captain William Harvey Sellers (1827-1874) married Harriet S. Cone Sellers (1830-1905) in 1853 and had four children. Their oldest daughter, Rosa Harriet Sellers (1859-1938) graduated from Augusta Female Seminary (now Mary Baldwin College) in 1876, before returning to Texas. In 1891, Rosa H. Sellers married William Fairfax Gray in 1891, and the couple had four children together. In 1899, the Gray family relocated to Homewood, Virginia, with their children, though only two of their children survived to adulthood. Rosa Argyle Gray (b. 1893) married Augustus Henry Drewry, and the couple moved to Surry County, Virginia, where they lived with their two children. Alan Fairfax Gray (1899-1961?) attended classes at William and Mary and returned in 1921 to teach courses in business and Spanish. Alan F. Gray travelled extensively, living in Brazil, New York, and Florida before returning to Virginia in 1937.
Scope and Content
Papers, 1847-1965, of the Sellers family consist of correspondence, photographs, diaries and ledgers, financial and business papers, genealogical notes, legal papers, drawings, and writings of the Sellers family. Collection also includes maps, travel brochures and postcards, newspaper clippings, wallets, jewelry, and Sellers family nameplates.
Contents List
- Correspondence, 1850-1965., Extent: 16 boxes. (Box 1-16)
  Correspondence, 1858-1965, is primarily comprised of letters, cards, invitations, postcards, and other materials addressed to and collected by Rosa Sellers Gray. Correspondents include Capt. William Harvey Sellers, Harriet Cone Sellers, Robert Henry (R.H.) Sellers, Lilly Sellers Rogers, William Fairfax Gray, Alan Fairfax Gray, Rosa Argyle Gray, and extended family members and friends. Topics include familial relationships, current events, health and wellness, career changes, travels and relocations, urban and rural life, and general small talk and gossip. In addition to providing insight into the daily life of the Sellers, Gray, and other families, cards and invitations showcase changes to art and design. Series is arranged chronologically; undated correspondence is located at the end of the series and is arranged topically.
  - Correspondence, 1858-1885. (Box 1, Folder 1)
  - Correspondence, 1890-June 1891. (Box 1, Folder 2)
  - Correspondence, July 1891-1892. (Box 1, Folder 3)
  - Correspondence, January 1893-April 1893. (Box 1, Folder 4)
  - Correspondence, May 1893-October 1893. (Box 1, Folder 5)
  - Correspondence, November 1893-March 1894. (Box 1, Folder 6)
  - Correspondence, May 1894-February 1896. (Box 1, Folder 7)
  - Correspondence, April 1896-April 1897. (Box 2, Folder 1)
  - Correspondence, June 1897-December 1905. (Box 2, Folder 2)
  - Correspondence, January 1906-May 1909. (Box 2, Folder 3)
  - Correspondence, July 1909-May 1910. (Box 2, Folder 4)
  - Correspondence, September 1910-April 1911. (Box 2, Folder 5)
  - Correspondence, May 1911-December 1913. (Box 2, Folder 6)
  - Correspondence, 1914-1918. (Box 2, Folder 7)
  - Correspondence, March 1919-December 1920. (Box 3, Folder 1)
  - Correspondence, January 1921-December 1922. (Box 3, Folder 2)
  - Correspondence, December 1922-December 1923. (Box 3, Folder 3)
  - Correspondence, March 1924-November 1924. (Box 3, Folder 4)
  - Correspondence, December 1924. (Box 3, Folder 5)
  - Correspondence, February 1925-November 1925. (Box 3, Folder 6)
  - Correspondence, November 1925-December 1925. (Box 3, Folder 7)
  - Correspondence, 1926. (Box 4, Folder 1)
  - Correspondence, 1927. (Box 4, Folder 2)
  - Correspondence, January 1928-June 1928. (Box 4, Folder 3)
  - Correspondence, July 1928. (Box 4, Folder 4)
  - Correspondence, July 1928-November 1928. (Box 4, Folder 5)
  - Correspondence, December 1928-March 1929. (Box 4, Folder 6)
  - Correspondence, April 1929-May 1929. (Box 4, Folder 7)
  - Correspondence, July 1929-October 1929. (Box 5, Folder 1)
  - Correspondence, November 1929-December 1929. (Box 5, Folder 2)
  - Correspondence, December 1929. (Box 5, Folder 3)
  - Correspondence, January 1930-February 1930. (Box 5, Folder 4)
  - Correspondence, March 1930-May 1930. (Box 5, Folder 5)
  - Correspondence, May 1930-June 1930. (Box 5, Folder 6)
  - Correspondence, July 1930. (Box 5, Folder 7)
  - Correspondence, August 1930-October 1930. (Box 6, Folder 1)
  - Correspondence, November 1930-December 1930. (Box 6, Folder 2)
  - Correspondence, December 1930. (Box 6, Folder 3)
  - Correspondence, December 1930-Feburary 1931. (Box 6, Folder 4)
  - Correspondence, March 1931. (Box 6, Folder 5)
  - Correspondence, April 1931-June 1931. (Box 6, Folder 6)
  - Correspondence, July 1931-September 1931. (Box 7, Folder 1)
  - Correspondence, October 1931. (Box 0S-2, Folder 6)
  - Correspondence, October 1931-November 1931. (Box 7, Folder 2)
  - Correspondence, December 1931. (Box 7, Folder 3)
  - Correspondence, January 1932-February 1932. (Box 7, Folder 4)
  - Correspondence, March 1931-April 1932. (Box 7, Folder 5)
  - Correspondence, May 1932-June 1932. (Box 7, Folder 6)
  - Correspondence, July 1932-August 1932. (Box 7, Folder 7)
  - Correspondence, August 1932-September 1932. (Box 8, Folder 1)
  - Correspondence, October 1932. (Box 8, Folder 2)
  - Correspondence, November 1932-December 1932. (Box 8, Folder 3)
  - Correspondence, December 1932. (Box 8, Folder 4)
  - Correspondence, January 1933-March 1933. (Box 8, Folder 5)
  - Correspondence, April 1933-May 1933. (Box 8, Folder 6)
  - Correspondence, June 1933-July 1933. (Box 8, Folder 7)
  - Correspondence, August 1933-September 1933. (Box 9, Folder 1)
  - Correspondence, October 1933-December 1933. (Box 9, Folder 2)
  - Correspondence, December 1933. (Box 9, Folder 3)
  - Correspondence, January 1934-February 1934. (Box 9, Folder 4)
  - Correspondence, March 1934-April 1934. (Box 9, Folder 5)
  - Correspondence, Mary 1934-June 1934. (Box 9, Folder 6)
  - Correspondence, July 1934-August 1934. (Box 10, Folder 1)
  - Correspondence, August 1934-October 1934. (Box 10, Folder 2)
  - Correspondence, November 1934-December 1934. (Box 10, Folder 3)
  - Correspondence, December 1934. (Box 10, Folder 4)
  - Correspondence, December 1934. (Box 10, Folder 5)
  - Correspondence, January 1935. (Box 10, Folder 6)
  - Correspondence, February 1935. (Box 10, Folder 7)
  - Correspondence, March 1935. (Box 11, Folder 1)
  - Correspondence, April 1935. (Box 11, Folder 2)
  - Correspondence, May 1935. (Box 11, Folder 3)
  - Correspondence, June 1935-August 1935. (Box 11, Folder 4)
  - Correspondence, August 1935. (Box 11, Folder 5)
  - Correspondence, September 1935-Ocober 1935. (Box 11, Folder 6)
  - Correspondence, November 1935. (Box 11, Folder 7)
  - Correspondence, December 1935. (Box 12, Folder 1)
  - Correspondence, January 1936-February 1936. (Box 12, Folder 2)
  - Correspondence, March 1936-June 1936. (Box 12, Folder 3)
  - Correspondence, July 1936-August 1936. (Box 12, Folder 4)
  - Correspondence, September 1936-November 1936. (Box 12, Folder 5)
  - Correspondence, December 1936. (Box 12, Folder 6)
  - Correspondence, December 1936-January 1937. (Box 13, Folder 1)
  - Correspondence, February 1937-May 1937. (Box 13, Folder 2)
  - Correspondence, May 1937-June 1937. (Box 13, Folder 3)
  - Correspondence, July 1937-September 1937. (Box 13, Folder 4)
  - Correspondence, October 1937-November 1937. (Box 13, Folder 5)
  - Correspondence, December 1937. (Box 13, Folder 6)
  - Correspondence, January 1938-February 1938. (Box 13, Folder 7)
  - Correspondence, March 1938-May 1939. (Box 14, Folder 1)
  - Correspondence, June 1938-September 1938. (Box 14, Folder 2)
  - Correspondence, October 1938-December 1938. (Box 14, Folder 3)
  - Correspondence, January 1939-May 1939. (Box 14, Folder 4)
  - Correspondence, June 1939-March 1965. (Box 14, Folder 5)
  - Correspondence, undated. (Box 14, Folder 6)
  - Correspondence, undated. (Box 15, Folder 1)
  - Correspondence, undated. (Box OS-2, Folder 9)
  - Postcards, undated. (Box 15, Folder 2)
  - Cards and Invitations, undated. (Box 15, Folder 3)
  - Cards and Invitations, undated. (Box 15, Folder 4)
  - Cards and Invitations, undated. (Box 15, Folder 5)
  - Cards and Invitations, undated. (Box 15, Folder 6)
  - Cards and Invitations, undated. (Box 15, Folder 7)
  - Cards and Invitations, undated. (Box 16, Folder 1)
  - Cards and Invitations, undated. (Box 16, Folder 2)
  - Envelopes, undated. (Box 16, Folder 3)
- Photographs, 1852-1935., Extent: 9 boxes. (Box 16-24 and 0S-2)
  Photographs, 1847-1935 and undated, includes photographs of the Sellers, Gray, Rogers, and Cone families, as well as many images of miscellaneous identified and unidentified men, women, and children. This series also contains photographs of landscapes and buildings in Virginia, Texas, New York, Jordon, Mexico, Brazil, Italy, and Norway. In addition, contained in this series are undated X-rays, convex miniature portraits, post-mortem photographs dating from 1858, and portraits taken by Richmond photographer George A. Brown, renowned for his portraits of African-Americans. Photographs are arranged by topic, and then chronologically when possible.
  - Sellers Family Photographs, 1852-1880. (Box 16, Folder 4)
  - Framed Sellers Family Post-Mortem Photographs, circa 1858. (Box 22)
  - Framed Sellers Family Photographs, circa 1860's- 1900's. (Box 23)
  - Convex Miniatures, 1873-1883. (Box 24)
  - Sellers Family Photographs, 1881-1889. (Box 16, Folder 5)
  - Sellers Family Photograph, 1883. (Box 0S-2, Folder 3)
  - Sellers Family Photographs, 1890-1935. (Box 16, Folder 6)
  - Sellers Family Photographs, undated. (Box 17, Folder 1)
  - Gray Family Photographs, 1878-1902. (Box 17, Folder 2)
  - Gray Family Photographs, 1908-1935. (Box 17, Folder 3)
  - Photograph of Rosa A. Gray, 1910. (Box OS-2, Folder 5)
  - Gray Family Photographs, undated. (Box 17, Folder 4)
  - Rogers Family Photographs, 1886-1890. (Box 17, Folder 5)
  - Rogers Family Photographs, 1892-1935 and undated. (Box 18, Folder 1)
  - Cone Family Photographs, 1847 and undated. (Box 18, Folder 2)
  - Photographs by Alan F. Gray, 1921. (Box 18, Folder 3)
  - Photographs of Alan and Joan Gray's Trip to Brazil, 1930 and undated. (Box 18, Folder 4)
  - George A. Brown photographs, undated. (Box 18, Folder 5)
  - Photographs of Miscellaneous Identified Women, 1876-1899. (Box 18, Folder 6)
  - Photographs of Miscellaneous Identified Women, undated. (Box 18, Folder 7)
  - Photographs of Miscellaneous Identified Men, 1873-1886. (Box 19, Folder 1)
  - Photographs of Miscellaneous Identified Men, 1887-1905. (Box 19, Folder 2)
  - Photographs of Miscellaneous Identified Men, undated. (Box 19, Folder 3)
  - Photographs of Miscellaneous Identified Children, 1883-1935. (Box 19, Folder 4)
  - Photographs of Miscellaneous Identified Children, undated. (Box 19, Folder 5)
  - Photographs of Unidentified Women, undated. (Box 19, Folder 6)
  - Photographs of Unidentified Women, undated. (Box 20, Folder 1)
  - Photographs of Unidentified Men, undated. (Box 20, Folder 2)
  - Photographs of Unidentified Men, undated. (Box 20, Folder 3)
  - Photographs of Unidentified Children, undated. (Box 20, Folder 4)
  - Photographs of Unidentified Children, undated. (Box 20, Folder 5)
  - Photographs of Unidentified Children, undated. (Box 20, Folder 6)
  - Photographs of Unidentified Groups and Couples, undated. (Box 21, Folder 1)
  - Photographs of Unidentified People and Animals, undated. (Box 21, Folder 2)
  - Photographs of Richmond and Lexington, Virginia undated. (Box 21, Folder 3)
  - Photographs of Galvenston and Fort Worth, Texas undated. (Box 21, Folder 4)
  - Photographs of Europe, 1904 and undated. (Box 21, Folder 5)
  - Photographs of Saratoga, New York 1920. (Box 21, Folder 6)
  - Photographs of Mexico, undated. (Box 21, Folder 7)
  - Photograph of Jordon, undated. (Box 21, Folder 8)
  - Photographs of Unidentified Landscapes, undated. (Box 21, Folder 9)
  - Photographs of Houses, 1920. (Box 21, Folder 10)
  - Photographs of Unidentified Buildings, undated. (Box 21, Folder 11)
  - Photographs of Boats, Automobiles, and Airplanes undated. (Box 21, Folder 12)
  - Miscellaneous Photographs, undated. (Box 21, Folder 13)
  - X-Rays, undated. (Box 21, Folder 14)
  - Photograph of Evans and Cora Gray, undated. (Box OS-2, Folder 7)
  - Photograph of Delta Psi Fraternity undated. (Box OS-2, Folder 8)
- Ledgers and Books, 1874-1921., Extent: 5 boxes. (Box 25-29)
  Ledgers, 1874-1938, is primarily comprised of notebooks and diaries authored by Rosa Sellers Gray. Rosa S. Gray's notebooks include address books, letter registers, personal diaries, and baby books written by Rosa and William Gray for their children. The ledgers of Rosa S. Gray commence prior to her matriculation into the Augusta Female Seminary in 1876, and end several years before her death, in 1935. Also included are anonymous journals and scrapbooks, a scrapbook created in 1921 by Jennie E. Dunbar, several account and inventory books, and the Sellers Family Bible.
  - Journal of Rosa Sellers, 1874. (Box 25, Folder 1)
  - Address Book of Rosa Sellers, 1890. (Box 25, Folder 2)
  - Letter Register of Rosa Sellers, 1890. (Box 25, Folder 3)
  - Address Book of Rosa Sellers, 1874. (Box 25, Folder 4)
  - Diary of Rosa Sellers Gray, 1891-1898. (Box 25, Folder 5)
  - Diary of Rosa S. Gray for William E. Gray, 1895-1898. (Box 25, Folder 6)
  - Diary of Rosa S. Gray and William F. Gray for Henry S. Gray, 1897-1921. (Box 25, Folder 7)
  - Diary of Rosa S. Gray for Alan F. Gray, 1898-1918. (Box 26, Folder 1)
  - Diary of Rosa S. Gray, 1898. (Box 26, Folder 2)
  - Diary of Rosa S. Gray, 1899-1901. (Box 26, Folder 3)
  - Diary of Rosa S. Gray for William E. Gray, 1899-1918. (Box 26, Folder 4)
  - Account Book, 1901. (Box 26, Folder 5)
  - Diary of Rosa S. Gray, 1901-1902. (Box 26, Folder 6)
  - Journal of Rosa S. Gray, 1903. (Box 26, Folder 7)
  - Diary of Rosa S. Gray, 1903. (Box 26, Folder 8)
  - Diary of Rosa S. Gray, 1903. (Box 26, Folder 9)
  - Diary of Rosa S. Gray, 1903-1911. (Box 26, Folder 10)
  - Anonymous Journal, 1907. (Box 27, Folder 1)
  - Journal of Rosa S. Gray, 1910. (Box 27, Folder 2)
  - Diary of Rosa S. Gray, 1911-1918. (Box 27, Folder 3)
  - Scrapbook of Jennie E. Dunbar, 1921. (Box 27, Folder 4)
  - Account Book of Emily A. Williams, 1920-1925. (Box 27, Folder 5)
  - Diary of Rosa S. Gray, 1922. (Box 27, Folder 6)
  - Diary of Rosa S. Gray for Alan F. Gray, 1926-1934. (Box 28, Folder 1)
  - Lawns and Fine Turf Corp. Account Book, 1927. (Box 28, Folder 2)
  - Inventory Ledger of Alan Gray, 1938. (Box 28, Folder 3)
  - Journal of Rosa S. Gray undated. (Box 28, Folder 4)
  - Anonymous Notebook, undated. (Box 28, Folder 5)
  - Anonymous School Composition Notebook, undated. (Box 28, Folder 6)
  - Seed Warehouse Ledger, undated. (Box 28, Folder 7)
  - Anonymous Diary and Account Book, undated. (Box 28, Folder 8)
  - Anonymous Notebook, undated. (Box 28, Folder 9)
  - Anonymous Notebook, undated. (Box 28, Folder 10)
  - Anonymous Notebook, undated. (Box 28, Folder 11)
  - Sellers Family Bible, undated. (Box 29, Folder 1)
- General Papers, 1849-1935., Extent: 1 box. (Box 30 and OS-2)
  General Papers, 1849-1935, contain the personal, business, financial, and legal papers of assorted members of the Sellers, Gray, and Cone families. Included in this series are a genealogy of the Ellis Family of Virginia, an 1859 phrenological survey of Rosa S. Gray's grandmother Sophronia C. Cone, report cards and diplomas of Rosa S. Gray, and recollections of Capt. William Harvey Sellers, written by members of the Fifth Texas Regiment. Also included are the business papers of the Homewood Farm Company (William F. Gray's company) and Lawn and Fine Turf, Inc., a business run by Alan F. Gray in Richmond. Papers also include personal and literary writings of Alan F. Gray, as well as miscellaneous drawings, sketches, and notes.
  - A Memorandum of the Ellis Family of Virginia, 1849. (Box 30, Folder 1)
  - Phrenological Survey of Sophronia C. Cone, 1859. (Box 30, Folder 2)
  - William H. Sellers Financial Papers, 1871-1894. (Box 30, Folder 3)
  - Reciept from L. Heyniger and Co. 1872. (Box OS-2, Folder 1)
  - Miscellaneous Reciepts, 1872-1928. (Box 30, Folder 4)
  - Rosa Sellers Report Cards, 1873. (Box 30, Folder 5)
  - Diplomas of Rosa Sellers, 1876. (Box OS-2, Folder 2)
  - Checks 1906. (Box 30, Folder 6)
  - Rosa S. Gray Account Balance 1909-1911. (Box OS-2, Folder 4)
  - Writings, 1912, 1935, and undated. (Box 30, Folder 7)
  - Private Papers of Alan F. Gray, 1915-1939 and undated. (Box 30, Folder 8)
  - Recollections of William Harvey Sellers, furnished by members of the Fifth Texas Regiment, 1916. (Box 30, Folder 9)
  - Methods and Costs of Obtaining Charters in Virginia, 1923. (Box 30, Folder 10)
  - Virginia Corporation Law, 1924. (Box 30, Folder 11)
  - Annual Record: Gamma Chapter, The Pi Kappa Alpha Fraternity, 1924. (Box 30, Folder 12)
  - Lawns and Fine Turf, Inc. 1926-1928 and undated. (Box 30, Folder 13)
  - Deposits, 1927. (Box 30, Folder 14)
  - Mary Baldwin Newsletters, 1929. (Box 30, Folder 15)
  - Miscellaneous Legal Papers, 1931-1939. (Box 30, Folder 16)
  - "Procedure for Appraisal of Sound Value of Buildings," by Alan F. Gray undated. (Box 30, Folder 17)
  - The Homewood Farm Company, undated. (Box 30, Folder 18)
  - Miscellaneous Financial Papers, undated. (Box 30, Folder 19)
  - Drawings, undated. (Box 30, Folder 20)
  - Notes, undated. (Box 30, Folder 21)
  - "David and Goliath", undated. (Box OS-2, Folder 10)
- Ephemera, 1881-1938., Extent: 4 boxes. (Box 31-33 AND OS-3)
  Ephemera, 1881-1938, is comprised of maps, blank local and non-local postcards, daily calendars of Rosa S. Gray, business cards, advertisements, and menus. This series also contains tickets, brochures, and other miscellaneous items collected during Rosa and William Gray's 1891 honeymoon, as well as printed images, and travel brochures from across the United States and Japan. This series is arranged chronologically, and undated items are placed at the end of the series.
  - Pamphlets and Programs, 1881-1938 and undated. (Box 31, Folder 1)
  - Calendar, 1890. (Box 31, Folder 2)
  - Mementos of Rosa and William Gray's Honeymoon in Colorado, 1891. (Box 31, Folder 3)
  - Calendars, 1894-1905. (Box 31, Folder 4)
  - Calendar, 1937. (Box 31, Folder 5)
  - Calendar, January 1938-June 1938. (Box 31, Folder 6)
  - Calendar, July 1938-December 1938. (Box 31, Folder 7)
  - Sellers Family Name Cards, undated. (Box 31, Folder 8)
  - Maps of Virginia, undated. (Box 31, Folder 9)
  - Travel Brochures, United States, undated. (Box 32, Folder 1)
  - Travel Brochure, Japan, undated. (Box 32, Folder 2)
  - Blank Virgnia and Washington, D.C. postcards, undated. (Box 32, Folder 3)
  - Blank non-local postcards, undated. (Box 32, Folder 4)
  - Blank Miscellaneous postcards,. (Box 32, Folder 5)
  - Christmas Ephemera, undated. (Box 32, Folder 6)
  - Business Cards and Advertisements, undated. (Box 32, Folder 7)
  - Blank Menus, undated. (Box 32, Folder 8)
  - Charles Taber and Co. Images, undated. (Box 32, Folder 9)
  - Images, undated. (Box 32, Folder 10)
  - Images, undated. (Box 33, Folder 1)
  - Images, undated. (Box 33, Folder 2)
  - Flowers, undated. (Box OS-2, Folder 11)
  - Souvenir Folder, Roanoke Virginia, undated. (Box OS-3, Folder 1)
  - Gulf, Colorado, and Sante Fe Railway Map, undated. (Box OS-3, Folder 2)
  - Rand McNally Standard Map of Virginia undated. (Box OS-3, Folder 3)
  - Clarksburg, West Virginia Grand Caverns Map, undated. (Box OS-3, Folder 4)
  - Map of James River and Vicinity, undated. (Box OS-3, Folder 5)
  - Map of James River Day Route, undated. (Box OS-3, Folder 6)
  - Map of James River Day Route, undated. (Box OS-3, Folder 7)
  - Historical Map of Virginia, undated. (Box OS-3, Folder 8)
  - South America, Furness Prince Line Map, undated. (Box OS-3, Folder 9)
  - South America and the Four Princes Map, undated. (Box OS-3, Folder 10)
  - South America Munson Steam Line, undated. (Box OS-3, Folder 11)
  - McCormick Map of the World, undated. (Box OS-3, Folder 12)
  - Oceano Atlantico Map, undated. (Box OS-3, Folder 13)
- Newspapers, 1863-1946., Extent: 2 boxes. (Box 33 and OS-1)
  Newspapers, 1863-1946, primarily contain newspaper clippings relating to the Sellers family, the British Royal Family, and World War II. The majority of the clippings are taken from Richmond, Virginia newspapers, particularly the Richmond Times Dispatch and the Richmond News Leader. This series also contains several issues of newspapers from North Carolina, as well as a 1926 edition of the Chinese newspaper, the Eastern Sun Times.
  - Newspaper Clippings- Sellers Family, 1863, 1905, and undated. (Box 33, Folder 3)
  - Newspaper clippings-Poems, 1906, 1910, and undated. (Box 33, Folder 4)
  - Newspaper Clippings-Miscellaneous, 1912-1946 and undated. (Box 33, Folder 5)
  - Newspaper Clippings-Photographs and sketches, 1925, 1938 and undated. (Box 33, Folder 6)
  - Newspaper- The Eastern Times, 1926. (Box OS-1, Folder 1)
  - Newspaper Clippings- British Royal Family, January 1936-February 1936. (Box 33, Folder 7)
  - Newspaper- The Charlotte News, 1938. (Box OS-1, Folder 2)
  - Newspaper- The Citizen and the Times, 1939. (Box OS-1, Folder 3)
  - Newspaper- Charlotte Sunday Observer, 1941. (Box OS-1, Folder 4)
  - Newspaper- The Winston-Salem Journal, January, 1942. (Box OS-1, Folder 5)
  - Newspaper Clippings- "Bataan's Diary", June 1942. (Box 33, Folder 8)
  - Newspaper Clippings-Health and wellness, January 1943 and undated. (Box 33, Folder 9)
  - Newspaper Clippings-World War II, 1943, 1944, and undated. (Box 33, Folder 10)
  - Newspaper Clippings of Mrs. W. W. Moore, 1944. (Box 33, Folder 11)
  - Newspaper Clippings-Lt. Col. W. E. Dyess, Feburary 1944-March 1944 and undated. (Box 33, Folder 12)
  - Newspaper- The Winston-Salem Journal October 1944. (Box OS-1, Folder 6)
  - Newspaper- The Charlotte Observer October 1944. (Box OS-1, Folder 6)
- Artifacts,, undated., Extent: 3 boxes. (Box 34-36)
  Artifacts, undated, include wallets, jewelry, and name plates of the Sellers family. This series also contains several tintypes of the Sellers family.
  - Wallets, undated. (Box 34)
  - Jewelry and Accessories, undated. (Box 35)
  - Tintype, undated. (Box 36, Folder 1)
  - Tintype, undated. (Box 36, Folder 2)
  - Tintype, undated. (Box 36, Folder 3)
  - "Mrs. William Fairfax Gray" Name Plate, undated. (Box 36, Folder 4)
  - "Mrs. Harriet Sellers" Name Plate, undated. (Box 36, Folder 5)
  - "Miss Sellers" Name Plate, undated. (Box 36, Folder 6)
  - "Miss Sellers" Name Plate, undated. (Box 36, Folder 7)